ecourts.gov.in 2018-05-13

# Privacy Policy - eCourt India Services

Though all efforts have been made to ensure the accuracy of the content on this website, the same should not be construed as a statement of law or used for any legal purposes. e-Committee, Supreme Court of India accepts no responsibility in relation to the accuracy, completeness, usefulness or otherwise, of the contents. Users are advised to verify/check any information, and to obtain any appropriate professional advice before acting on the information provided on this website. 

e-Courts website does not automatically capture any specific personal information from any user (like name, phone no. or e-mail address) that allows e-Committee to identify any user individually when users visit the site. Users can generally visit the site without revealing Personal Information, unless users choose to provide such information. 

* ## **Site Visit data**

This website records user’s visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes -users server’s address; the name of the top-level domain from which users access the Internet (for example, .gov, .com, .in, etc.); the type of browser users used; the date and time users access the site; the pages users have accessed. We will not identify users or their browsing activities, except when a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service provider’s logs. 
* ## **Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of software code that an Internet web site sends to user’s browser when users access information at that site. This website does not use cookies. 
* ## **Collection of Personal Information**

If users are asked for any other Personal Information users will be informed how it will be used if users choose to give it. If at any time users believe the principles referred to in this privacy statement have not been followed, or have any other comments on these principles, please notify the webmaster through the contact us page.   
**Note:** The use of the term "Personal Information" in this privacy statement refers to any information from which user’s identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained.
